usefile.com 2014-06-25

# UseFile - Easy way to share your files

Privacy Policy

**UseFile Privacy Policy**  
UseFile is a provider of online file storage service. Your use of the UseFile site is governed by UseFile Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the service we provide, about the ways how the personal information you submit to us may be used, and how this information is protected on our website.

UseFile ("us" or "we") respects the privacy of the visitors on its website. We may update this policy from time to time, so we ask you to check the policy regularly. We will notify you about significant changes by placing a prominent notice on this page and other places we find appropriate.

**Your information during the registration**  
UseFile stores an e-mail address you specify when you register with us, and your name if it is indicated in the user profile. UseFile does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies. Also, IP addresses are logged and used to identify our visitors as well as manage download limitations and user sessions.

**Your account password**  
Please note that it is your responsibility to keep the password confidential, so do not share it with anyone. If you use a public PC, make sure you log out prior to leaving UseFile site. You are solely responsible for keeping your password inviolable.

**Certain exceptional disclosures**  
We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. The disclosure of personal information may be required by court or law enforcement officials.

**Your account at our service**  
When you upload a file to our server, we give you a unique URL to download the file. We do not share download URLs with anyone; however we will provide the file to any browser requesting the file by its unique URL address.

We reserve a right to review your account content for violations of our Terms and Conditions. If we determine that your files violate the Terms and Conditions, we may ban your account and will attempt to contact you. We reserve the right to cancel your account and remove the files from our servers.

We do not own your account content, and will access your files for troubleshooting only.All your files are allowed to be downloaded only according to the security settings you define. We guarantee safety of your files, for that purpose we make backups of all files.

**Using cookies**  
UseFile uses cookies in order to track and analyze preferences of our users and, as a result, improve our site. A cookie is an encrypted number, generated when you visit any site that supports sessions. This cookie is saved permanently on your computer. This data does not contain any secure information (just an encrypted string). Additionally, we set a cookie when you log in to make further logging into our system a little easier. No other website can access any information about you from the cookies we may store on your local computer. We do not share cookies or any other type of information with any other companies. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie.We also collect such information as your operating system, browser version and the size of your screen. We use these details for marketing purposes also. This information is collected in the form of the usual web server logs and cookies.

**Third party cookies**  
In case of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Access to your information**  
You have the right to access, upload and download your files and access and correct your personal information at any time. You may also grant access to your account files to other users through sharing link lists or file download links.

If you want to change any personal information provided to us, feel free to contact our support team at support@UseFile.com

**How we protect your information**  
Any information collected and processed within UseFile is treated with the utmost confidentiality. UseFile will not sell or rent out any personal information gathered from clients. We will make no public release of any personal information that is collected through our proprietary file sharing tool. All client-specific information gathered through us will be the property of the user. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy and to ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put into place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information that we collect online. We encrypt the information you submit to UseFile with VeriSign 256-bit SSL certificate.Automated and scheduled backups of your files make the service secure and safe for you.

**Credit card security**  
All purchases on UseFile are handled by third party payment systems. UseFile does not arrange and/or save numbers or any information from your credit cards.

**External links**  
If any part of the UseFile website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information.

**Contact information**  
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://usefile.com/contact.html).

We use top of the line data centers to host your files. So you can download files faster than any other cloud storage.

We now support a HTML5 mobile optimized video player. You can also embed video player in your site! [Sample video](http://usefile.com/fb2sq8v0ekn2/bunny.mp4.html)

We provide unlimited storage for our premium users. So, store all your videos, music, and other files without worrying about space
